Suddenly Explorers! The Suddenly Explorers!
Please take care of our gastronomic osterlust, Mr. and Mrs. Ikinari Talk!
Please take care of our gastronomic ostertorast, Mr. Ikinari Talk! We are the Ikinari Expedition!
Today, we have a special version!
We usually go inside E-Beans for the first time.
We are going out for the first time.
Out?
Out!
My first essay!
Yes, I know!
It's an outing version of an expedition.
Today we are at the Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium!
As a part of Endochen's 95th anniversary project, we're going to visit the Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium.
This is a collaboration between Ginari Talk and Umi-no-Mori Aquarium.
Today is the day of the Ginari Talk Aquarium!
What's that?
What's that? Fish!
Today, we're going to do a little filming for the Expedition team here.
Today's project is
Let's try our hand at announcing the museum.
So, until now, we've been trying to get each member of the Tork team to do an announcement for His Majesty's Eavins, and the only ones left were Ataka and Aya.
The only one who hasn't done it is Aya.
The other 8 members have already finished.
I don't know if I remember.
They didn't do it!
We just made taro stew two years ago.
It was delicious.
Yes, it was.
So it's a bird...
An aquarium!
Oh no! I'm sorry!
I'm going to challenge you to make an announcement in the aquarium.
I'll leave it to you, Ms. Kawatani, to decide what to say.
So you're going to leave it all up to me?
You can do that here, too?
No, it's fine.
I said it!
I did.
I'm filming!
I told you!
Proof, proof.
I said it. I said it.
I'm in charge.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to be the closing announcement and the closing announcement for the general public.
It'll also be an announcement for the audience coming to the stadium concert afterwards.
Please do it before you do anything else.
Yes, please do it as usual.
Then let's get moving.
What?
That's the way to do it.
You're filming so fast, but time is running out.
We're running out of time.
You know what I mean.
We don't have time for this.
Thank you so much for your time.
We're moving, let's go. I want to go on the jump.
Let's go, let's do it after the jump.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Yes, we've arrived at the information desk on the first floor.
Here we are.
Look at this. It's a little visual.
They're all cute.
Scary.
The Sea Forest Aquarium will be closing soon,
Are you listening to me?
Sorry, I was taking a selfie.
I would like to ask Mr. Kawatani, the closing announcer, to let me in.
I'll do my best.
Let's go.
Wow, it's amazing we can get in here. Sure.
It's a general information. Back general information.
Amazing. You couldn't get in here if you didn't cut all the way through.
Well, then, at the right time, Mr. Kawa-ya.
Please announce that the museum is closed for the day.
I'll be right back.
Thank you for visiting the Sea Forest Aquarium today.
Thank you very much.
We would like to inform our guests
Our hours of operation today are
until 6:00 p.m. today.
Please be careful not to forget anything when you leave.
Please be careful when you leave.
Thank you for visiting Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium today.
Thank you very much for visiting Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium today.
Great! The aquarium is now completely closed!
This microphone is light!
Can I have a word with you today? Speak up, everybody.
Suddenly we're at the Northeast Aquarium.
Shut up!
I didn't know you were that kind of guy.
Wait a minute.
Oh! It's light!
It's light!
It's okay!
We're suddenly at the Tohoku Aquarium today, aren't we?
The aquarium will be closed after this.
Mr. Tohoku!
There's an event after this.
Starting at 6:30.
There are guests waiting in line for it.
There are some people outside.
It looks like it's going to be a live concert.
It's a good location, isn't it?
Here's a little video.
Everybody's jumping up and down a little bit.
So I'm going to go outside and make an announcement.
I'm going to have him give a little speech in front of the crowd, and then I'm going to make an announcement about what's going to happen after this.
I'm going to make an announcement at 6:30, so I'm going to go outside and speak.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous when it happens.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for watching.
The next event will begin at 6:00 p.m.
Please wait a little longer.
I hope you all enjoyed the noon event.
Wait a minute, I was too busy with the camera and my voice was too quiet.
Did you enjoy it?
Yes!
It was great.
I hope everyone who saw this had a really good time.
Yes!
It's Moruru.
I don't know what to do.
Yes, yes, yes.
This event is...
We've always been a big fan of
Sendai Ekimae e-Bing
who runs the Sendai Ekimae e-Bing.
who runs e-bing in front of Sendai station
celebrated the 95th anniversary of its foundation.
95 years ago, it was 1929, the year of the Great Redemption of the World?
How do you read that?
Grand Public?
Grand Pope?
Grand Pope.
Grand Publique.
A little bit of the Great Public.
That's how I feel today.
It's like the year of the Great Depression.
It's been 95 years since the company was founded in such a year.
I'm very happy.
I want to live to be 95 years old.
No, I don't.
I don't think so.
Wait a minute.
Well, then, let's all say congratulations.
Let's end it.
Okay.
Oh, it's not over.
I want to live! Well then, see you at the Sea Forest Stadium!
That's all for now, thank you for watching at the Ujiran Waterworks Concert by Kazuto Mizutani!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
That's about it.
Bye!
Announcements have been made.
How was it? Hi, Mom.
It's going to be loud.
They're coming.
They're probably going to eat us.
Well, this isn't my first time.
I guess this is the first time I've done all the announcements by myself.
Yes, that's right.
I had help from Shinji and Miyu.
Well, it feels good to be in charge of the world.
I thought of it myself, but I didn't tell you!
What? That sentence.
Captain thought of it.
We're doing the Kannayanan series at D-Beans.
It's over, you know.
The first season.
What should we do? Captain.
Second Season
You still have a lot of staff.
Maru-chan?
to do it?
Give them extras.
And then...
Can you stop talking?
Then I'd like to announce the start of the show.
The show starts? In the morning? The museum was closed.
Open?
Not for me.
But can the eight of us go on?
You're leaving?
But if there's an opportunity, we'll announce it.
Let's do a second season.
It was fun.
I'm getting to be an announcer.
I'm waking up to the feeling of being an announcer
I'm not sure if my brain is up to it.
I'm glad everyone had their own personality.
Now that we've finished the series of announcements in the museum, I'd like to invite you all to join us at the Sea Forest Waterworks for some announcements.
I hope you all try announcing inside the museum at the Sea Forest Water Agency!
Boo-boo!
Boo-boo-boo!
I've been here, I've been here, I've been here, I've been here, I've been here, I've been here, I've been here, I've been here...
I'd like to end today's exploration
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Bye bye
Great.
Bye-bye.
See you soon.